<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CONAIR</string>
    <string name="main_home">Home</string>
    <string name="main_trend">Trend</string>
    <string name="main_discover">Discover</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="discover_diet" formatted="false">Are there any foods I shouldn\'t eat during pregnancy?\nRaw seafood, such as oysters or uncooked sushi.Pate, raw or undercooked meat, poultry, and eggs. All are possible sources of bacteria that can harm your unborn child.\nMany women choose to avoid alcoholic drinks during pregnancy.\n\nOr linking to other website.
    </string>
    <string name="discover_diet2" formatted="false">
        Getting into a routine with your baby is a personal thing. You\'ll learn to read your baby\'s cues to develop a pattern of eating, sleeping, and playing that meets your little one\'s needs and works for your family.\n1\– and 2\–month\–old babies need:\n12 to 24 ounces of breast milk or formula, though this amount may be as high as 32 ounces.\nAbout 16 hours of sleep – including nighttime sleep and naps. Three naps during the day (morning, afternoon, and evening) is typical.\n3 and 4 months most babies need:\n6 or 7 ounces of breast milk or formula per feeding, though limit this amount to 32 ounces in a 24\–hour period.\nSome parents start solid foods like infant cereal when their baby is 4 months old.\nAbout 15 hours of sleep in a 24\–hour period – this includes nighttime sleep and naps. Three naps during the day (morning, afternoon, and evening) is typical.\n5 and 6 months most babies need:\nUp to 32 ounces of breast milk or formula in a 24\–hour period.\nAbout 14 hours of sleep in a 24\–hour period – this includes nighttime sleep and naps.\n9 and 10 months most babies need:\nSolid foods three times a day, plus about 24 to 32 ounces of breast milk or formula in a 24\–hour period.\nAbout 14 hours of sleep in a 24\–hour period – this includes nighttime sleep and naps. Two naps during the day (morning and afternoon) is typical.\n
    </string>
    <string name="discover_prep" formatted="false">
        How do I lose weight after I give birth?\n\–  You\'ll likely lose about half of your pregnancy weight gain in the first six weeks after delivery. The baby accounts for about 7.5 pounds, and the amniotic fluid, placenta, and extra body fluids and blood in your body add up to another 8 to 12 pounds.\nFor the rest, remember that it took nine months to put on the weight, and it can take just as long or longer for it to come off. A healthy diet combined with regular exercise is the best way to shed the pounds – and keep them off.\nDon\'t start cutting calories right away, though. Caring for a newborn requires lots of energy – and that means giving your body the nutrition it needs.
    </string>
    <string name="dicover_prep2" formatted="false">Track baby\'s growth at home \nWeigh your baby. \nMeasure your baby\'s length.\nMeasure the circumference of your baby\'s head.\nOnce you have these measurements, to find out roughly how your baby compares with other babies the same age.\n\nWhat can my baby\'s growth chart tell me?\nYour baby\'s growth chart can give you a general picture of how your baby is developing physically. By comparing your baby\'s measurements – weight, length, and head circumference – to those of other children the same age and sex and to these same measurements from previous checkups, your child\'s doctor can determine whether your baby is growing in a healthy way.\nBut don\'t get too hung up on your baby\'s percentiles. Although the current growth charts are a vast improvement over earlier charts, they\'re not the last word on how your baby is doing. The most important thing is that your baby is growing at a steady, appropriate rate over time, not that she\'s hit some magic number.\nPercentiles in a growth chart aren\'t like grades in school. A lower percentile doesn\'t mean there\'s anything wrong with your baby.\nLet\'s say both parents are shorter than average, and your baby grows up to have the same stature. It would be perfectly normal for her to rank consistently in the 10th percentile for height and weight as she grows up.\nThere are times when gaining or losing faster than usual is a good thing. If your baby was underweight, for example, it may be a good sign that she\'s gaining ounces faster than she\'s growing inches.\n\nOr linking to below babycenter website.\nhttps://www.babycenter.com/0_growth\–charts\–taking\–your\–babys\–measurements_1620.bc?page=3\nThe basics of baby schedules: Why, when, and how to start a routine\nWhy should I have a schedule for my baby?\nA baby\'s needs aren\'t that complicated – food, sleep, play, and love pretty much sums it up. But knowing what your baby requires when, and how much of it, can be a real challenge. Not to mention balancing your baby\'s needs with your own and those of older children and other family members.\nMany parents find that getting into a regular routine or schedule with their baby makes life much easier: It\'s almost like developing a personalized how\–to manual for your child.\nWhen can I start?\nExperts disagree on when and how to establish a routine – and even on whether you need a set schedule for your baby. But many experts, say that babies are ready for a general schedule between 2 and 4 months of age.\nHow to start a routine\nMost infants\' sleeping and feeding habits become more consistent and predictable after three or four months. You may want to take this opportunity to encourage your baby to follow a more defined schedule.\nYour baby may fall into fairly predictable patterns long before this, however. If that\'s the case, you can gently encourage your baby\'s emerging routine.\nTracking your child\'s eating, sleeping, and alert times can give you an understanding of his natural rhythms and enable you to pinpoint developing patterns. In the days following delivery, many parents begin to note when their baby feeds, when he poops and pees, when he sleeps and for how long, and so on.\nTo log your baby\'s daily routine, you can use a notebook and pen, a computer spreadsheet, or any number of great apps.
    </string>
    <string name="novice_msg" formatted="false">1, Establish your goals. \n2, Choose efficient exercises. Some exercises will be more efficient than others, and choosing these more efficient exercises means that the amount of time that you do spend exercising will really count.\n3 Eating and Drinking Right.\n4 Let your body rest. \n\– Sleeping too little has also been linked to overeating.\n\– Be sure that you don’t deprive your body of sleep energy or you will make it up in calories.\n5 Get a check\–up.\n6 Have belief in yourself.\n\– Do not care what other people think. If you are determined and believe that you can achieve your goal of staying fit then you can! Know that feeling when you feel great and strive to reach that goal everyday. Motivate yourself by wanting to continue on this path of fitness and health.\n

    </string>
    <string name="muscle_msg" formatted="false">Muscle building in the right way\n1.Make realistic goals.  \nGoals should be measurable and specific.\nAlso include a timeline for your long\–term goals.\n2 Track your progress. \n3 Talk to a dietitian (Or take the suggestion of our Apps). \n4．Increase your caloric intake. \n5．Choose calorie\–dense foods. \nTry eating: full\–fat dairy products, olive oil, avocado, nuts and nut butters.Avoid eating sugary junk food to increase your calorie intake. Eating cookies, candy, donuts, etc. may help you gain weight, but not in a healthy way.\n6．Eat adequate protein. Eat healthy carbs immediately before and after your workouts.．Consider drinking a protein supplement.\n“protein powder 6 times a day”,\n“load up on creatine for 6 days”,\n“be sure and eat within 45 minutes of your workout”,\n“never workout longer than 45 minutes”,\n“eat 1 gram of protein per pound of bodyweight”.\n
    </string>
    <string name="exercise_msg" formatted="false">Maintaining Your New Lifestyle\n1, Establish your goals. Goals can help you stay focused on maintaining your ideal body weight, body fat, muscle, and fitness levels.\n2, Keep going to the gym Being Active Every Day\nA, Walk more.\nB, Change your desk set\–up.\nC, Use a ball chair.\nD, Have walk meetings.\nF, Do more chores\nG, Walk on your breaks\nFitting Exercise into Your Schedule\n1, Split up your exercises.\n2, Choose efficient exercises. Some exercises will be more efficient than others, and choosing these more efficient exercises means that the amount of time that you do spend exercising will really count.\nSquats. Squats work on your core and leg muscles\nPlanks. , for maintaining your core, leg, shoulder, neck, and upper arm muscles.\nBurpees. ,exercise all areas of your body.\n
    </string>
    <string name="discover_diet3" formatted="false">Maintaining a Balanced Diet\n1, Get rid of any junk food. It is one of the most important components of a fit lifestyle. Many people ignore it, but if you exercise and eat a lot of junk food you will not get any fitter. This is because the junk food turns to fat almost immediately. Junk foods contain little to no nutrition and are high in sodium and sugar. \nFoods to avoid are: \nHigh in sugar: Donuts, cakes, cookies, pudding, cereals, canned and dried fruits, and sodas.\nHigh in fat: Processed meats, butter, hydrogenated oil (coconut and palm kernel), shortening, cheese and animal fats.\nHigh in cholesterol: Egg yolk, fried foods and mayonnaise.\nAvoid anything containing: High fructose corn syrup (HFCS) and Monosodium glutamate 味精 (MSG).\n\n2, Eat healthy. You will find that maintaining a healthy and balanced diet can increase energy and productivity, boost your metabolism and make you a happier person because you will be consuming the nutrients and vitamins your body needs.\nFoods to eat are: \nFresh fruits and vegetables: Melons, bananas, apples, oranges, carrots, onions, broccoli and corn, etc. If you make a salad, the more colorful the better!\nOrganic meats: Fish, poultry and beef for protein. Instead of frying the meats, try to bake them with extra virgin olive oil or lemon juice with herbs.\nGrains: Whole wheat toast, oatmeal and pastas.\nFoods high in protein: Tofu, soy beans, egg whites, nuts, cottage cheese and quinoa.\nFoods high in fiber:  Cooked lentils, black beans, green peas, pears, raspberries and oat bran.\n\n3 ,Drink 1.5~2 liters (0.5 US gal) of water each day. Water keeps you hydrated and promotes optimal metabolic activity.\n
    </string>wo
    <string name="trend_msg" formatted="false">1, 9 weeks Pregnancy \nAt week\'s end, your baby measures about 2.3 centimeters long. In both shape and size, she resembles a peapod and weighs less than 2 grams. The eyelids are fused and won\'t open until week 27. The wrists are more developed, ankles have formed, and the fingers and toes are clearly visible. Arms are growing longer and bend at the elbows. By week\'s end, the inner workings of the ears are complete.\n2,  16 weeks Pregnancy - feel baby\'s first movements?\nYou\'ll probably become aware of some movement at about 18 weeks to 20 weeks of your pregnancy.\nIf this is your first pregnancy, it may take you a while to realise that those gentle fluttering feelings (quickening) in your tummy are your baby\'s movements. Being aware of these first, tiny sensations inside is an exciting landmark for most mums-to-be.\nIf you\'ve had a baby before, you\'ll know the tell-tale signs, and may notice your baby moving around as early as 16 weeks. \n
    </string>
    <string name="trend_msg2" formatted="false">Your Baby\'s Developmental Milestones\nFind out when your baby might walk, talk, crawl, grasp objects, and hit other fantastic firsts from birth to 6 months and 7 to 12 months.\nDevelopmental milestones at 1 month\nYour role\nEnjoy getting to know your baby: Cuddle her, talk to her, and learn how she signals when she\'s sleepy or hungry. Be attentive and responsive. You can\'t spoil a baby!\nDevelopmental milestones at 3 months\nYour role\nDon\'t worry about spoiling your baby: Responding to him promptly helps him feel secure and loved. You can help him learn to soothe himself by guiding his thumb to his mouth or offering him a pacifier.\nContinue to make tummy time part of his daily routine so he can practice his new skills and strengthen his muscles. When he\'s on his tummy, give him toys and safe objects he can reach for, hold, and explore.\n\nDevelopmental milestones at 4 to 7 months\nShe views the world in full color now and can see farther.\nYour baby is fully engaged with the world now: She smiles, laughs, and has babbling "conversations" with you. And she\'s on the move \– by 7 months she can probably roll to her tummy and back again, sit without your help, and support her weight with her legs well enough to bounce when you hold her.\nYour role\nYour baby thrives on the interactions she has with you\nRead together every day, naming the objects you see in books and around you.\nWork on establishing a routine for sleeping, feeding, and playtime.\nMilestones: 8 to 12 months\nLook at your baby go! He\'s become an eager explorer, and it might surprise you how quickly he can get around when he crawls or scoots. He can sit on his own now and grabs anything he can to pull himself up to standing and "cruise." He might even take some solo steps before his first birthday.\nYour role\nKeep talking to your baby: This is a critical time for his language development. Describe your routine, what you\'re doing now and what you\'re going to do next, and what you see. Describing how you think your baby is feeling helps him learn emotions. Keep reading together and play peekaboo, hide-and-seek, and turn-taking games.\n
    </string>
    <string name="trend_preg">You gain less than the recommended amount of weight\nIf you start out underweight, can mean a higher risk of delivering a low-birth-weight baby (less than 5.5 pounds). \n</string>
    <string name="msg">1. Tips for a Good Pregnancy \nFetal movement is also a status indicator to track the baby\’s growth!\nIn general, you can relax if you can feel 10 fetal movements during day time. \n\n2. Is it Ok to Exercise?\nWalking, yoga, and swimming are great options, at about 30 minutes a day.\n \n3. Regularly see your doctor\nDon\’t overwork, and overstress/overtire yourself.\n\n4. As much as possible,make sure you always have company especially if you are having a difficult pregnancy.\n\n5. Pregnancy tip: soothe aching muscles\nTry gently massaging your lower back or use a heat pack, hot water bottle or warmed facecloth. \n
    </string>
    <string name="trend_preg1">9 weeks Pregnancy\nIn both shape and size, she resembles a peapod and weighs less than 2 grams. \n</string>
    <string name="trend_preg2">12 weeks pregnant\nYour little one\'s teeny toes can curl, her brain is growing furiously, and her kidneys are starting to excrete urine. \n</string>
    <string name="trend_preg3">13 weeks pregnant\nIt\'s the last week of the first trimester! Your baby now has exquisite fingerprints and is almost 3 inches long. \n</string>
    <string name="trend_preg4">14 weeks pregnant\nYour baby\'s tiny features are making different expressions. And you may be feeling more energetic and less nauseated. \n</string>
    <string name="trend_preg5">19 weeks pregnant\nGo ahead and sing: Your baby may be able to hear you! And if your sides are aching, it could be round ligament pain. \n</string>
    <string name="trend_preg6">27 weeks pregnant\nFeel a tickle? It may be your baby hiccupping. He\'s also opening and closing his eyes and even sucking his fingers. \n</string>
    <string name="trend_preg7">28 weeks pregnant\nWelcome to your last trimester! Your developing baby\'s eyes may be able to see light filtering in through your womb. \n</string>
    <string name="trend_preg8">30 weeks pregnant\nYour baby now weighs almost 3 pounds. Meanwhile, you may be battling mood swings, clumsiness, and fatigue. \n</string>
    <string name="trend_preg9">39 weeks pregnant\nYour baby is full term this week and waiting to greet the world! If your water breaks, call your healthcare provider. \n</string>
    <string name="discover_msg1">#1 Why you need folic acid?\n\nBecause it\'s very difficult to eat enough foods rich in the vitamin to supply the amount that experts recommend you take in pregnancy.\nIt helps make DNA (the body\'s genetic material) and is a critical component of spinal fluid.\nWhat are the best food sources?\nLeafy green vegetables are a good source, so try to have a large bowl of salad daily.\n
    </string>
    <string name="discover_msg3">#2 Dietary Guidelines recommend that you enjoy a wide variety of nutritious foods every day from these food groups:\nVegetables of different types and colour and legumes\nFruit\nDrink milk and special formula for pregnant women\nTake the best prenatal vitamins recommended by your doctor\nGrain including breads, rice, pasta, noodles, polenta, oats, mostly wholegrain\nInclude lean meat, fish, poultry, nuts, legumes\nKeep away junk foods and unhealthy stuff\nAnd drink plenty of water\n
    </string>
    <string name="discover_msg4">#3 Are there any foods I shouldn\'t eat during pregnancy?\nRaw seafood, such as oysters or uncooked sushi.\nPate, raw or undercooked meat, poultry, and eggs. All are possible sources of bacteria that can harm your unborn child.\nCheeses with a white, \'mouldy\' rind, such as Brie and Camembert, blue-veined cheeses like Stilton.\nMany women choose to avoid alcoholic drinks during pregnancy.\n
    </string>
    <string name="discover_msg5">Eating well: 0-8 weeks\nFocus on folic acid\nLunch: broccoli and pea soup/ Tuna nicoise salad\nSnack: orange with stem ginger and dates\nDinner: beef and black eye bean casserole\n\nEating well: 9-12 weeks\nEat little and often. Focus on B vitamins\nLunch: avocado and warm chicken salad\nSnack: Greek yogurt with ginger or honey and almonds\nDinner: creamy tuna and salmon pie\nSnack: Anzac biscuits with macadamias\n</string>
    <string name="discover_msg6">Eating well: 17-20 weeks\nOmega 3 essential fatty acids\nLunch: super salad\nSnack: oaty cranberry and orange cookies\nDinner: salmon with pine nuts and lime\nLamb, quinoa and rocket salad\n\nEating well: 25-28 weeks\nCalcium and vitamin D\nLunch: ciabatta with haloumi, basil and sundried tomatoes\nSnack: hummous with pitta bread\nDinner: mushroom and celery pasta bake\n </string>
    <string name="discover_msg7">Eating well: 29-32 weeks\nVegetarian and pregnant\nLunch: pitta bread with baby spinach, Gruyère and grapes\nSnack: strawberry milk shake\nDinner: creamy chick pea curry\n\nEating well: 37-40 weeks\nEating and drinking in labour\nLunch: beetroot soup\nSnack: fruity flapjacks\nDinner: ragu sauce\n
</string>
    <string name="discover_msg2">Baby Registry Checklist\nNursery\nChanging table or pad\nCrib &amp; mattress\nBaby gear\nDiaperingBreastfeeding &amp; bottle feeding\nSolid feeding\nBathing\nClothing\nSleeping\nBaby soothers, toys &amp; entertainment\nSafety\nHealth\n\nLinking to the page \'BABY CENTER\'\nwebsite for the detail:\nhttps://www.babycenter.com/baby-registry-checklist
    </string>
    <string name="work_msg1">30 Minutes (around 2 kilometre ) burn  75 Calories
    </string>
    <string name="work_msg2">30 Minutes （around  8 kilometre ） burn 330 Calories
    </string>
    <string name="work_msg3"> 30 Minutes (around 4.5 kilometre ) burn 300 Calories
    </string>
    <string name="work_msg4">30 Minutes （around 1.5 kilometre ） burn 175 Calories
    </string>
    <string name="work_msg5">60 Minutes burn 432 Calories.
    </string>
    <string name="work_msg6">exercise all areas of your body. 12 reps with 4 sets burn 1968 Calories.\nComplete 7-12 reps with 3-4 sets resting somewhere between 1-2 minutes between sets.
    </string>
    <string name="work_msg7">work on your core and leg muscles. Burn 150 Calories per 30 minutes with 15 reps and rest  20 seconds.\n Activity Guide: This exercise is done by standing with your feet shoulder width apart and, keeping your back straight, bending your knees to lower your body as if you were sitting in a chair.
    </string>
    <string name="work_msg8">for maintaining your core, leg, shoulder, neck, and upper arm muscles. 1 minutes burn 21 Calories.Suggest 3-15 minutes.\n Activity Guide:  Planks are done by getting into something like a push-up position. However, instead of resting your upper body weight on your hands, rest your weight on your whole forearm instead and hold the position for as long as you can.\n
    </string>
    <string name="work_msg9">Burpees, exercise all areas of your body.  1 minutes take 7reps burn 10 Calories. It\’s better up to 10 reps 1 min.\n Activity Guide : This exercise is done by dropping from a standing position into a crouching position, thrusting your legs out backward into a push-up position (you can add an actual push-up if you want), jumping back into a crouching position, and then jumping up as high as you can (arms up).
    </string>
    <string name="trend_work">  Your Baby\'s Developmental Milestones\nFind out when your baby might walk, talk, crawl, grasp objects, and hit other fantastic firsts from birth to 6 months and 7 to 12 months.\nDevelopmental milestones at1 month\nYour role\nEnjoy getting to know your baby: Cuddle her, talk to her, and learn how she signals when she\'s sleepy or hungry. Be attentive and responsive. You can\'t spoil a baby!\nDevelopmental milestones at 3 months\nYour role\nDon\'t worry about spoiling your baby: Responding to him promptly helps him feel secure and loved. You can help him learn to soothe himself by guiding his thumb to his mouth or offering him a pacifier.\nContinue to make tummy time part of his daily routine so he can practice his new skills and strengthen his muscles. When he\'s on his tummy, give him toys and safe objects he can reach for, hold, and explore.\n\nDevelopmental milestones at 4 to 7 months\nShe views the world in full color now and can see farther.\nYour baby is fully engaged with the world now: She smiles, laughs, and has babbling \"conversations\" with you. And she\'s on the move – by 7 months she can probably roll to her tummy and back again, sit without your help, and support her weight with her legs well enough to bounce when you hold her.\nYour role\nYour baby thrives on the interactions she has with you\nRead together every day, naming the objects you see in books and around you.\nWork on establishing a routine for sleeping, feeding, and playtime.\nMilestones: 8 to 12 months\nLook at your baby go! He\'s become an eager explorer, and it might surprise you how quickly he can get around when he crawls or scoots. He can sit on his own now and grabs anything he can to pull himself up to standing and "cruise." He might even take some solo steps before his first birthday.\nYour role\nKeep talking to your baby: This is a critical time for his language development. Describe your routine, what you\'re doing now and what you\'re going to do next, and what you see. Describing how you think your baby is feeling helps him learn emotions. Keep reading together and play peekaboo, hide-and-seek, and turn-taking games.\n
    </string>
    <string name="discover_baby1">Getting into a routine with your baby is a personal thing.\n\n1- and 2-month-old babies need:\n12 to 24 ounces of breast milk or formula, though this amount may be as high as 32 ounces.\nAbout 16 hours of sleep – including nighttime sleep and naps. Three naps during the day (morning, afternoon, and evening) is typical.\n
    </string>
    <string name="discover_baby2">3 and 4 months most babies need:\n6 or 7 ounces of breast milk or formula per feeding, though limit this amount to 32 ounces in a 24-hour period.\nSome parents start solid foods like infant cereal when their baby is 4 months old.\nAbout 15 hours of sleep in a 24-hour period – this includes nighttime sleep and naps. Three naps during the day (morning, afternoon, and evening) is typical.\n
    </string>
    <string name="discover_baby3">5 and 6 months most babies need:\nUp to 32 ounces of breast milk or formula in a 24-hour period.\nAbout 14 hours of sleep in a 24-hour period – this includes nighttime sleep and naps.\n\n9 and 10 months most babies need:\nSolid foods three times a day, plus about 24 to 32 ounces of breast milk or formula in a 24-hour period.\nAbout 14 hours of sleep in a 24-hour period – this includes nighttime sleep and naps. Two naps during the day (morning and afternoon) is typical.\n
    </string>
    <string name="discover_baby21">The basics of baby schedules: Why, when, and how to start a routine\nWhy should I have a schedule for my baby?\nA baby\'s needs aren\'t that complicated – food, sleep, play, and love pretty much sums it up.\nMany parents find that getting into a regular routine or schedule with their baby  makes life much easier: It\'s almost like developing a personalized how-to manual for your child.\n
    </string>
    <string name="discover_baby22">When can I start?\nExperts disagree on when and how to establish a routine – and even on whether you need a set schedule for your baby.\nBut many experts, say that babies are ready for a general schedule between 2 and 4 months of age.\n
    </string>
    <string name="discover_baby23">How to start a routine\nMost infants\' sleeping and feeding habits become more consistent and predictable after three or four months.\nYou may want to take this opportunity to encourage your baby to follow a more defined schedule.\nYour baby may fall into fairly predictable patterns long before this, however.\nIf that\'s the case, you can gently encourage your baby\'s emerging routine.\nTracking your child\'s eating, sleeping, and alert times can give you an understanding of his natural rhythms and enable you to pinpoint developing patterns.\nIn the days following delivery, many parents begin to note when their baby feeds, when he poops and pees, when he sleeps and for how long, and so on.\nTo log your baby\'s daily routine, you can use a notebook and pen, a computer spreadsheet, or any number of great apps.\n
    </string>
    <string name="discover_baby24">Track baby\'s growth at home\nWeigh your baby.\nMeasure your baby\'s length.\nMeasure the circumference of your baby\'s head.\nOnce you have these measurements, to find out roughly how your baby compares with other babies the same age.\n
    </string>
    <string name="discover_baby25">What can my baby\'s growth chart tell me?\nYour baby\'s growth chart can give you a general picture of how  your baby is developing physically.\nBut don\'t get too hung up on your baby\'s percentiles. Although the current growth charts are a vast improvement over earlier charts, they\'re not the last word on how your baby is doing.\nThe most important thing is that your baby is growing at a steady, appropriate rate over time, not that she\'s hit some magic number.\nPercentiles in a growth chart aren\'t like grades in school. A lower percentile doesn\'t mean there\'s anything wrong with your baby.\nLet\'s say both parents are shorter than average, and your baby grows up to have the same stature.\n
    </string>
    <string name="discover_baby26">Or linking to below babycenter website.\nhttps://www.babycenter.com/0_growth-charts-taking-your-babys-measurements_1620.bc?page=3
    </string>
    <string name="discover_work1">1. Establish your goals\n\n2. Choose efficient exercises\n\n3. Eating and Drinking Right\n\n4. Let your body rest\n\n5. Get a check-up\n\n6. Have belief in yourself\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="discover_work2">Muscle building in the right way\nMake realistic goals\nTrack your progress\nTalk to a dietitian\nIncrease your caloric intake\nChoose calorie-dense foods\nEat adequate protein\nEat healthy carbs immediately before and after your workouts\nConsider drinking a protein supplement: “1 gram of protein per pound of bodyweight”\n
    </string>
    <string name="discover_work3">Maintaining Your New Lifestyle\n1. Establish your goals\nGoals can help you stay focused on maintaining your ideal body weight, body fat, muscle, and fitness levels.\n\n2. Keep going to the gym Being Active Every Day\nA, Walk more\nB, Change your desk set-up\nC, Use a ball chair\nD, Have walk meetings\nF, Do more chores\nG, Walk on your breaks\n
    </string>
    <string name="discover_work4">Maintaining a Balanced Diet\n1.  Get rid of any junk food. It is one of the most important components of a fit lifestyle.\nMany people ignore it, but if you exercise and eat a lot of junk food you will not get any fitter.\nThis is because the junk food turns to fat almost immediately.\n\nFoods to avoid are:\nHigh in sugar: Donuts, cakes, cookies, pudding, cereals, canned and dried fruits, and sodas.\nHigh in fat: Processed meats, butter, hydrogenated oil (coconut and palm kernel), shortening, cheese and animal fats.\nHigh in cholesterol: Egg yolk, fried foods and mayonnaise.\nAvoid anything containing: High fructose corn syrup (HFCS) and Monosodium glutamate (MSG).\n
    </string>
    <string name="discover_work5">2. Eat healthy\nYou will find that maintaining a healthy and balanced diet can increase energy and productivity, boost your metabolism and make you a happier person because you will be consuming the nutrients and vitamins your body needs.\n\nFoods to eat are: \n Fresh fruits and vegetables: Melons, bananas, apples, oranges, carrots, onions, broccoli and corn, etc. If you make a salad, the more colorful the better!\nOrganic meats: Fish, poultry and beef for protein. Instead of frying the meats, try to bake them with extra virgin olive oil or lemon juice with herbs.\nGrains: Whole wheat toast, oatmeal and pastas.\nFoods high in protein: Tofu, soy beans, egg whites, nuts, cottage cheese and quinoa.\nFoods high in fiber:  Cooked lentils, black beans, green peas, pears, raspberries and oat bran.\n
    </string>
    <string name="discover_work6">3. Drink 1.5~2 liters (0.5 US gal) of water each day.\nWater keeps you hydrated and promotes optimal metabolic activity.\n
    </string>
    <string name="discover_work7">Eating Right\n1, Make the lifestyle change.\n2, Reduce trans fats and simple carbs.\n3, Add in healthy fats.\n4, Get plenty of protein.\n5, Eat properly portioned, balanced meals.\nCut Back on Sugars and Starches\n\nGenerally, about ⅓ of your plate should be fruits and vegetables and ⅓ of your plate should be grains. The final third should be a mix of protein and low-fat dairy (cottage cheese, eggs, milk, etc).\n
    </string>
    <string name="discover_work8">Choose calorie-dense foods , Increase your caloric intake \nTry eating: full-fat dairy products, olive oil, avocado, nuts and nut butters.\nDrizzle olive oil or put a pat of butter on your foods after you\'ve prepared them. \nPut avocados on your salad or serve with scrambled eggs in the morning. \nBlend peanut butter into protein shakes or have it as an afternoon snack.\nAvoid eating sugary junk food to increase your calorie intake.\nEating cookies, candy, donuts, etc. may help you gain weight, but not in a healthy way.\n
    </string>
</resources>
